# Fabian Mora

### Developer en Móvil Multimedia

fabianmorar1223@gmail.com

#### Extracto

I'm a designer, a fan of social networks, new technologies and startups, I have experience at branding, photography, ui and ux design, web design and web development. Every day I like to create, think and develop experiences that simplify the daily lives of people.

# Experiencia

Developer en Móvil Multimedia

enero de 2016 - Actualidad (4 meses)

Developed using technologies like: PHP, Angulas.js, Ionic, codeigniter, MySQL, HTML5, CSS3, Grunt y Sass

### Graphic Designer en Frelancer

octubre de 2015 - Actualidad(7 meses)

Development and project management as: Editorial Photography Web Design and Development Branding UX/UI Social media packaging design Graphic design

## Graphic Designer en My own company

enero de 2014 - julio de 2014 (7 meses)

Design and conceptualization of shirts, prints by serigraphy technique, I learned and run all the processes required to make the product.

# Graphic Designer en Sueños Hoteleros

enero de 2013 - diciembre de 2013 (1 año)

Design and development of advertising campaigns to social media, printed materials, websites and digital advertising.

#### Cursos

Cursos independientes

Advanced JavaScript Kyle Simpson

Development of creative thinking Clandestina

SMACSS: Scalable Modular Architecture for CSS

Jonathan Snook

Linear Feature Animation production Digital animation

Development startups AUGE

# Reconocimientos y premios

#### **GSB 2014 Finalists: Education Track**

GlobalStartupBattle diciembre de 2014

Top 15 Latin American and the Caribbean as a project of technological innovation in the education category

### **Publicaciones**

### Ticos compiten para desarrollar app que disminuirá embarazos en adolescentes

crhoy 28 de noviembre de 2014

Autores: Fabian Mora

Un grupo de ocho costarricenses universitarios compiten en el #GlobalStartupBattle, para impulsar una iniciativa que pretende disminuir la cifra de embarazos adolescentes en nuestro país y a nivel de Latinoamérica.

### Jóvenes ticos desarrollarán videojuego para combatir el cambio climático

ameliarueda 24 de febrero de 2015

Autores: Fabian Mora

Estudiantes del Centro de Tecnología y Artes Visuales del Parque de La Libertad (CETAV) desarrollarán un videojuego para combatir el cambio climático.

# **Proyectos**

#### **Neoland**

noviembre de 2014 a Actualidad

Miembros: Fabian Mora, Ana Javier Quintero

NEOLAND is a program of comprehensive sex education, through an anonymous and virtual experience.

#### Game Jam

febrero de 2015 a Actualidad

Miembros: Fabian Mora, Alexis Pizarro

Climate Change, will be the centerpiece under which students will develop an educational video game CETAV with recognized experts Olivier Lejade from France, Matthias Loewe from Germany and the national company Fair Play Labs. The project financed by the Franco-German Cultural Fund, takes the points of convergence between France, Germany and Costa Rica on climate change issues. It also has the support of experts on Climate Change UNDP.

# Experiencia de voluntariado

### Fundación Acción Joven en Trabajo comunal

noviembre de 2014 - Actualidad

Experience that allowed me to grow as a person, develop soft skills and allowed me to get in touch with people that with a little guidance can accomplish great things

## Idiomas

**Español** (Competencia bilingüe o nativa)

ingles (Competencia básica)

# Aptitudes y conocimientos

**Drupal** 

Diseño gráfico

**Graphic Design** 

Web Design

Diseño web

**Usability** 

Desarrollo web

**CSS** 

**Photoshop** 

**User Experience** 

**Visual Communication** 

**Web Development** 

**User Interface Design** 

**Photography** 

HTML5

WordPress

Diseño de la interfaz de usuario

Illustrator

**Social Media** 

**JavaScript** 

entrepreneurship

Experiencia del usuario

word

**Usabilidad** 

**Redes sociales** 

Fotografía

ionicframework

## Educación

cetav

Advanced technician, Desarrollo de páginas web, contenido digital/multimedia y recursos

informáticos, 2014 - 2015

Actividades y grupos: WorkShop Motion Capture en CR

Universidad de las Ciencias y el Arte de Costa Rica

Bachelor of design, Diseño gráfico, 2011 - 2016